Brother...
You've sure grown up, Yuliy.
I knew that there was no way I was wrong.
I knew you were my brother.
Why did you run from me on the roof without telling me anything?
I couldn't have talked to you then.
"Kill all Jaegers on sight."
That's one of the orders we vampires have been given.
Brother...
So you did become a vampire.
Yeah.
It's honestly absurd for me to be sitting with you right now.
You can smell them too, right?
Well, they don't have total trust in me.
When I shot you, my orders were to kill you.
I had no desire to end the life of my precious little brother,
so I intentionally missed your vitals.
Impressive, huh?
Why?
I thought you didn't use guns.
Ah, that's right, I once taught you how to hunt.
If I recall, I said not to use guns since they'll dull your sense of smell, right?
That doesn't apply to me now that I've become a vampire.
Yuliy.
Why did you become a Jaeger?
Do I really need to tell you?
It was for revenge.
I'm going to kill all those who took our mom and brethren away from us.
I see.
You're a Jaeger, and I'm a vampire.
As things are, we're eventually going to be forced to kill each other.
I thought you had been killed.
But now I've found you, my only living family,
and you're telling me that we have to kill each other.
I have no idea what I should say!
Then I'll say this as your brother.
Yuliy.
Forget about revenge.
If I'm to live
by inertia
There's probably nothing
wrong with giving up
But I don't want the night stolen from me
The moon shines down on me as if to comfort my shuttered heart
I'm left with only a cold blade
I'm just losing myself
I'm searching
Just like this planet that's lost everything
I don't think that I'm always right
But I'm not going to regret what I do now
Making just one wish, I fade into the night
This is Iba. I'm coming in.
General...
Sit here until we get to the next station.
Yes, sir.
Once we get there, we're going to have you call your parents.
Yes, sir. I'm sorry.
Miss Ryouko?
What are you doing on this train?
I'm—
I'm, well—
You see, I'm—
Would you like to eat this with me?
Forget about revenge?
What are you saying, brother?
I can tell just by looking into your eyes.
You're not cut out to be an avenger.
An avenger's eyes are filled with anger, hatred, sadness, and despair.
Yours are just those of an upset child.
That's not true!
My entire purpose in life has been to kill vampires!
Then why don't you kill me?
Are you going to drive all the other vampires to extinction first
and leave me for the very end?
I'm...
Come on!
Hurry up and kill me!
You want to kill every vampire that you can, as quickly as possible, right?
Then you'll never have a better chance then this one.
I won't try to stop you.
What's wrong?
Just stop, Yuliy.
You'll never be cold-hearted enough.
Just forget about it all.
Forget me, forget Dogville,
forget Mom.
And forget about the Ark.
The Ark?
If you still choose to appear before me as a Jaeger,
you'll no longer be my little brother.
You'll be my enemy.
Look at all those scars.
Iba. If you're here to deliver my death sentence, then I'm glad that it's you.
Please don't talk nonsense, General.
What exactly happened out there?
I've received a report that there was an accident at the exercises in Fuji—
There was no accident.
That was...
That was a one-sided slaughter.
Slaughter?
I let many men die last night.
I imagine that they just wanted us as lab rats from the start.
They?
Alma Company?
We were dancing in the palm of their hand.
We should have stayed away.
We should have never gotten involved with a monster with such a despicable origin.
General, what exactly—
We must not bring it into the capital.
Something must be done!
You can't mean...
It's on this train?
I see our prey, boss.
It's heading this way!
Let's go!
The hunt begins!
Chasing after your crush is a pretty aggressive move for a well-bred girl like you.
My crush?! No, it's not...
...like that.
It's just that I'm kind of interested in Yuliy...
That's what we call a crush.
No, it's—
Yuliy doesn't really get romance,
so I don't think it'll be easy making him yours.
No, I'm telling you that that's not...
On top of that, the worlds you live in are too different.
Yes, that!
That's what I'm interested in.
Is Yuliy—
Or, no.
Are you all doing some kind of dangerous work?
You've...
All right, then.
Why don't you take that food and go ask Yuliy yourself?
Don't try to change the—
What happened?
What on earth...
I, Momose Naotora, head of the Hyakko Party,
am claiming this train for the cause!
Th-The Hyakko Party!
Why are we stopped?
Someone call the conductor!
That's impossible.
It'll be okay.
What's going on?
Excuse me!
What happened?
A group claiming to be the
Hyakko Party have attacked the train!
The Hyakko Party?
The soldiers riding this train are currently attempting to prevent their advance!
Why would they...
Protecting the civilians is our top priority!
Don't let the attackers near the passenger cars!
Yes, sir!
Major Iba, could you go and help take command?
Yes, sir. Moving to assist!
Hurry, hurry!
Please don't push!
Dorothea, what should we—
Leave the rest to us.
You escape with the rest of the passengers!
What's wrong? You'll never hit me with shooting like that!
Come on, hit me!
Let's go!
For all the Hyakko Party's lofty claims about making the world better,
it would seem that they're no more noble then any other band of robbers.
Just because Lord Yevgraf is taken by you
doesn't mean that you can do whatever you please.
This commotion is all because you cut off their funding and turned a blind eye to the consequences.
There are Jaegers here as well.
Foolish, lowly humans.
They're nothing more than hyenas.
Or was there a wolf among them, too?
Let's leave this place to Klarwein.
Mikhail. How about you use those claws and fangs of yours for once?
Look out, they've taken the freight car!
Keep them away from the passenger car!
Hurry! Everyone with a gun get to the front!
Don't get separated! Stay in groups and go under the train!
Find Kershner!
He and his treasure should be on this train somewhere!
Boss!
What'd you find?
What's this strange suit of armor?
Could this be the new weapon they—
It moved.
Is it alive?
Some sort of mechanism?
Very entertaining!
I like it! Nicely done for a pack of monsters!
Right! Start the train!
And find Kershner!
Find him, tie him up, and throw him down at my feet!
Yeah!
He's done.
Let's get out of here!
Yuliy...
Hurry up and jump off, Miss!
Hurry!
I'm sorry!
Major, the train's changed tracks!
What?!
Are they planning on stealing this whole train?
Slaves!
Quickly, Ume!
Ume!
Are you all right?
Thanks, Mister.
Ume!
Mommy!
Brother...
Yuliy.
If you still choose to appear before me as a Jaeger,
you'll no longer be my little brother.
Even so...
Keep shooting! Don't give them an inch!
Don't falter! Show them what samurai are made of!
Yo, what the hell's that?
That's a lot of smoke.
Fallon, follow that train.
Hurry.
Roger that!
Fantastic!
Boss?
He used his body to protect us!
What an excellent fellow!
What's wrong, comrades? Stand up!
With him at our side, we'll never need to worry about...
Deary me!
Now, let's start the show!
All right, monster!
As my servant, wreck havoc to your heart's content!
The Showa Restoration is upon us!
The boss is dead!
They got the boss?
What the hell do we do now?
Well, I mean...
Hey, there's nobody in there!
So if we just leave it, it'll stop?
Crap!
The tire's blown!
What the hell's going on in there?
Dorothea?
What? There's no way.
You think I can't recognize my team members?
This is bad.
The rail ends up ahead.
And from here to there is all downhill.
But that means...
Fallon, give me the wheel!
Find Dorothea and Yuliy and then stop that train!
Dorothea!
Get here faster next time!
I think that's a bit unreasonable!
Disconnecting the car behind us should help a bit!
Go for it!
Nice! Put that beef to use!
Yuliy?
Yuliy!
Stop the train!
We're gonna run out of rail!
Everything you people do is crazy!
That jump was what's crazy!
It was surely fate that led us to meet here.
Please let me assist y—
Brother...
I thought I'd never meet you again.
Despite that,
Despite that, I always...
I always wanted to see you!
Are you not a vampire?
Even so,
you give off the same smell as them.
You're standing in my way.
If you're not going to move...
Major!
We're pulling back.
Regroup with the soldiers in the rear.
Oh, it's the nuisance from the other day!
You're...
Friend of yours?
He's a newspaper reporter who's been investigating us.
And why would that reporter happen to be carrying a gun?
It's for self-defense.
When you're chasing down risky leads, you...
Major!
Look out!
Miss Ryouko.
I've cut a person...
Don't worry. It's not a person.
According to his seven-year-old daughter,
the doctor turned into glowing ash and disappeared.
Impossible.
If you're a reporter, that'll probably make a better story than us.
What on earth is...
Never seen one before?
That there's a vampire.
Vampire?
I never even imagined that I'd get data on fighting Jaegers so soon!
Oh, shoot! There's no stopping him now!
Even after I said all that, you still came?
Fitting, since you've always been toddling after me.
Brother.
You can't stop anymore, can you?
I'll put you to rest now.
Yuliy.
If I ever end up like him,
I want you to be the one to kill me.
What are you talking about?
If you have the Ark...
If you have the Ark of Sirius, you'll be able to do it.
To kill, and to let live.
That's—
Brother...
Ten years.
We've had to take quite the detour.
But when compared to our coming thousand years...
Or rather...
Compared to our coming eternity,
it was but a moment.
What an unbearable end
I breath out, breath out, breath out, and stop
As I'm fleeing from this cruel world, I fall into a deep sleep
I hide behind the words "I'm doing my best"
But in the end I do nothing but look back
Even when I feel like I've been able to change,
Eventually I realize that the only thing that's changed is the position of the stars
I find myself wondering if everything would feel better if I just broke
Before I fade away while thinking of you,
If I dig out all of my pain then I'll be able to shine like a real star
Will I find a beautiful dream?
This is how we embrace hope
A way to live other than revenge...
Why is the Army involved? What the hell's going on?
I'll buy time if I have to.
Do you want to leave the Jaegers, Yuliy?
You're going to fight me!